(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Thomas had to write a story for class.
His English teacher wanted him to write a
story about anything.
He had no idea what to write.
He could not think of a good idea.
He wanted to do well on his assignment.
This was an important assignment.
It would count a lot towards his grade.
After a while, he decided to go outside.
He took a walk in the park.
The park gave him some inspiration.
He decided to write a story about a
family who was having a picnic in the
park.
His story would have a twist.
He would make the family get superpowers from
being in the park.
He ran home.
He was excited to write his story.